Coin-Operated Laundry
This is a coin-operated laundry.
No doubt about it,
this is a coin-operated laundry.
So then, how come...
Why the hell are you here, Sensei?!
Bon-Kyu-Bon
Why the hell are
you here, Sensei!?
Bon-Kyu-Bon
Kono mune ni...
(My Darling)
Futomomo ni...
(My body)
Nee, oshiri ni...
(My feeling)
Furetemitai no deshou?
Toboketemo mou muda dayo
(Your pretty boy)
(You fall in love)
Toboketemo mou muda dayo
Chanto kao ni kaitearu wa
(If I love)
(Together)
Anata wa yume no naka de watashi ni
Donna koto o shite niyaketeru no kashira?
('Cause I love you)
Guuzen ga kasanatte, naze ka anata ni hikarechatteru
Uh, baby, baby, touch me
Unmei ga kousa shite futari ga itsuka
Musubaretara dakishimete ne?
Subete ageru wa
Kareshi ni nattara ne
Darling
2nd Period
Sato, are you sheltering
from the rain, too?
Y-yeah...
On my way home from school,
it just started suddenly raining.
And now I'm soaking wet.
Y-you do seem to be drenched.
Seeing as there are dryers here,
why not dry your clothes?
Huh?!
These are the only clothes I've got.
Are you telling me to get naked?!
N-no!
How terrifying!
Being able to give off an intimidating air
even while wearing see-through clothing...
That's "Kojima the Demon" for you!
M-my clothes aren't that wet,
and I'd be happy to lend them to you.
Wh-what? Are you sure?
If she stays dressed that way, I'll end up
unintentionally peeking and put my life in danger...
That's what I was thinking, but...
Well, thank you, Sato.
Now I'm really gonna have
a hard time averting my eyes!
Seems the rain's not stopping, huh?
W-well, it's a storm that suddenly rose up,
so suspect it'll die down soon.
Sudden storms are often accompanied by thunder,
so they're no fun, huh, Sensei?
Are you, by chance, scared of thunder?
H-huh?! No way!
I'm a teacher, you know?!
The idea I could be so childish-
Sorry... I actually am scared of it.
I-I can see that!
Now, please get off of me!
Did that lightning just
now knock the power out?
And that must mean...
I knew it! The dryer stopped working.
I can't go home like this!
Well, let's try searching
for the circuit breaker!
Isn't that it?
Sure is high up there...
And there doesn't seem to be anything
we can use as a step stool...
Ah, I know!
How's it going?
I can almost reach it!
It's been a while since I've hoisted
someone onto my shoulders...
More than physically,
I don't think I can hold out mentally!
S-still haven't got it, Sensei?
Almost there....
Hold-!
M-my bad...
It's alright.
This feels slimy... Is it laundry detergent?
S-seems so...
Anyhow, let me try standing up again.
I'm gonna lift up your lower back a bit now.
Okay.
Hup!
Uh-oh!
I'm sorry!
W-wait! Don't pull on that!
The button's will...!
I... just grabbed Kojima's breasts...
They're so soft...
No, stop! Don't think about them!
W-wait... Sato...
Really...
now...
stop!
Good grief...
I'm sorry about that.
Still, what are we gonna do about
the circuit breaker, anyway?
I may have somehow escaped being killed,
but what was with her voice
being so seductive a moment ago?
Cool it, my son!
Oh, that's it!
This time, I'll put you on my shoulders!
No, that won't do.
Don't underestimate me!
I can lift the likes of you, you know!
That's not the issue! Now's
not a good time for me!
Hup!
S-Sato...
Something is,
uh... poking the back of my head...
The storm wasn't the only thing
that suddenly rose up...
Just kid-
What're you doing thrusting that thing
against me, you idiot?!
I'M SORRY!
Kawanuma-nishi
High School
3rd-Year
Student
Satou
Ichirou
Birthday:  May 10th
Height: 172cm
Weight: 58kg
Why the hell are you here?
This is my mother's family home.
No doubt about it,
this is my mother's family home.
So then, why...
is this happening?!
My mom asked you to babysit?!
Yeah. I'm also from this area,
and Saki-san really helped me out in the past.
Besides, I was already back here
visiting home over summer break,
so I had no reason to say no, right?
Sensei, I had no idea that you and
my mom know each other.
I mean, are you even capable of taking care
of a small child in the first place?
O-of course I can!
W-well, my intimidating aura
can even hush crying kids,
so just watch my babysitting techniques!
"Babysitting techniques," huh?
Look, come on over here to "Big Sister."
She's crying like it's
the end of the world...
To tell the truth, this is how it's been
going for a while now.
Whenever I come near her,
she starts crying immediately...
despite wanting small kids to like me!
Yeah?
In fact, earlier today my
parents told me to hurry up and
get married and give them some grandkids.
But, the reality is that,
the way things stand...
when I do have a baby,
it's gonna be pretty tough, right?
Marriage, huh?
Sensei, you're the earnest sort,
so I imagine you have high standards
when it comes to a partner.
Not really. They're pretty ordinary.
Someone who's younger, good at caring
for people, and who's liked by children.
Those three things are
all I've ever asked for.
Someone
who's younger
"Someone who's younger...
good at caring for people...
Good at caring
for people
Who's liked
by children
and who's liked by children."
Huh?
S-Sato, I didn't mean you!
In the first place, we're
teacher and student, right?!
Right you are! I know, okay?!
Oh, right! How about we play with her
in the water out in the yard?
Shio likes splashing about,
so she'll take a liking to you in no time!
O-oh, I see!
Well, guess I'll head to my parents' house
and grab my bathing suit!
O-okay! I'll get everything
ready in the meantime!
Ah... It's kinda nice to take a dip
like this once in a while.
Sure you're okay not
coming in yourself, Sato?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Or rather, if I get in there together with you,
it could turn out badly...
To think Kojima would wear
such a risque bathing suit!
Don't stare at me like that...
All I had at my parents' place was
a bathing suit from my school days.
Wait, why is my heart pounding?!
Don't forget this is "Kojima the Demon"!
Even so...
Oh, you're giggling now, huh?!
Today, Kojima seems different
from her usual self...
Look! Look!
Today, Kojima seems different from her usual self...
I wonder if this is how Kojima
is when she's off work...
If that's the case...!
What are you doing, Baby Sister?!
Look out!
S-sorry!
Th-that was my bad!
WHAT?!
I'll pull her off right away!
No, it's fine to let her be.
Why?!
The fact that she's suckling my breast
means that she sees me as a maternal figure.
That makes me happy, you know?
It means I have what it takes to be a mother.
Now I just need to find a partner!
"P-partner"?!
I-I don't mean you!
I-I know that!
Oh, Kana, thank you for today.
Don't mention it. I had a good time.
Come to think of it, I heard your folks
told you to hurry up and get married.
If you're looking for a partner, my son's all yours!
He's your type, right?
You look pretty sleepy.
S-Saki-san, what're you...?!
Well, it's time to eat, so go and
call your future husband!
Just kidding!
Please don't tease me like that.
Good grief...
We're teacher and student, you know!
Even so...
Ah, that was just an accident!
That doesn't count!
I-in the first place, they say these days
there are people who casually kiss their friends!
Th-that's right! So long
as we don't cross the line-
There, I've laid out the futon.
Let's hurry and go to bed.
Wh-wh-wha...?
Sensei?
You idiot!
Huh?
Can't you at least wait
until you graduate, idiot?!
Whaddya mean?!
Chiisana omoide demo
Dondon fukurande
Tayorinai senaka
Kizukeba me de otteita
Kyoukasho niwa nai
Honto no kimi no kimochi ga shiritai yo
Oshiete! Kyun, kyun, kyun, kyun!
Ano toki yorimo zutto muchuu
Chime nattemo tomaranai daisuki
Tokimeki! Run, run, run, run!
Hayatochirisuru koigokoro
Itsumo yumemichau
Kimi kara no ringo-iro memories